[{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980214224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":5611,"timeElapsed":36402},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980218124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3898,"timeElapsed":40302},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980226411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":8285,"timeElapsed":48589},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980234501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8089,"timeElapsed":56679},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980239073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4571,"timeElapsed":61251},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980242751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3676,"timeElapsed":64928},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980253380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":10627,"timeElapsed":75558},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980256922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3540,"timeElapsed":79100},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980259173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2250,"timeElapsed":81351},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980266313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":5535,"timeElapsed":88491},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980268837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2522,"timeElapsed":91015},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980270720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1881,"timeElapsed":92898},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980272704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1983,"timeElapsed":94882},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980275270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2565,"timeElapsed":97448},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980277568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2297,"timeElapsed":99746},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980280291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2721,"timeElapsed":102469},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980282340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2048,"timeElapsed":104518},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980284686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2344,"timeElapsed":106864},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980303760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":17561,"timeElapsed":125938},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980305268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1506,"timeElapsed":127446},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980307745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":2476,"timeElapsed":129923},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980309381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1634,"timeElapsed":131559},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980311467,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2085,"timeElapsed":133645},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980318203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6734,"timeElapsed":140381},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980319704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1499,"timeElapsed":141882},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2723,"timeElapsed":144606},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980323991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":1562,"timeElapsed":146169},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980325923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1930,"timeElapsed":148101},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980335071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":8216,"timeElapsed":157249},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980336577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1505,"timeElapsed":158755},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980338877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2298,"timeElapsed":161055},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980340110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1232,"timeElapsed":162288},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980342184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2073,"timeElapsed":164362},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1857,"timeElapsed":166220},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980345515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1471,"timeElapsed":167693},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347040,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1523,"timeElapsed":169218},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980348773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1731,"timeElapsed":170951},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980359263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":9319,"timeElapsed":181440},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980361246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1982,"timeElapsed":183424},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980362878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1631,"timeElapsed":185056},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980366003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3124,"timeElapsed":188181},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980368622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2618,"timeElapsed":190800},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980372524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3900,"timeElapsed":194702},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1545,"timeElapsed":196250},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980376049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1976,"timeElapsed":198227},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980378165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2114,"timeElapsed":200343},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980385040,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5729,"timeElapsed":207218},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":1407,"timeElapsed":208627},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980388671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2221,"timeElapsed":210849},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980390461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1788,"timeElapsed":212639},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980391988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1525,"timeElapsed":214166},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980393505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1516,"timeElapsed":215683},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980395399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1893,"timeElapsed":217577},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980397152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1751,"timeElapsed":219330},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2050,"timeElapsed":221382},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980406829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":6636,"timeElapsed":229007},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1846,"timeElapsed":230855},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980410647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1968,"timeElapsed":232824},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":1914,"timeElapsed":234740},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4872,"timeElapsed":239614},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1875,"timeElapsed":241491},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2201,"timeElapsed":243693},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980423255,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1738,"timeElapsed":245433},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3352,"timeElapsed":248786},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4101,"timeElapsed":252889},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980436650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4797,"timeElapsed":258828},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2444,"timeElapsed":261274},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1696,"timeElapsed":262972},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3565,"timeElapsed":266539},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2636,"timeElapsed":269176},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1826,"timeElapsed":271003},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2027,"timeElapsed":273032},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980455206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":4351,"timeElapsed":277384},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980457030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1822,"timeElapsed":279207},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3644,"timeElapsed":283994},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1815,"timeElapsed":285811},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980466304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2669,"timeElapsed":288482},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1977,"timeElapsed":290460},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1443,"timeElapsed":291905},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1399,"timeElapsed":293305},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980473776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2647,"timeElapsed":295954},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980475907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2129,"timeElapsed":298085},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980477688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1780,"timeElapsed":299866},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980485616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6659,"timeElapsed":307794},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980487287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1669,"timeElapsed":309465},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980489399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2111,"timeElapsed":311577},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980491456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2055,"timeElapsed":313634},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980493529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2072,"timeElapsed":315707},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":1635,"timeElapsed":317343},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980496585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1419,"timeElapsed":318763},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1869,"timeElapsed":320634},{"subjectID":"b6pbnys2d8","prolificID":"66ec5904d71fbac55031aaf5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247f13c4a2d74f3f0b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1845,"timeElapsed":322480}]